Contact

+61 7 5641 1865 (Work) pradlashodoski423@outlook.c

www.linkedin.com/in/prad-lashodoski-416465246 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

React.js Vue.js

Laravel

Prad Lashodoski

Full Stack Developer

Rockhampton, Queensland, Australia

Summary

I am senior fullstack developer with 9 years experience.

I know well about React, Vue, Node, Laravel, Spring Boot, Django, CI, C#, ASP.NET.

Also, I have strong knowledge about clouding services like AWS, Azure, Google Firebase.

I also very familiar with RESTful APIs, Mysql, MsSQL, SQLite PostgreSQL, MongoDB, AWS DynamoDB.

Experience

Tech2B

Full-stack Developer

January 2019 - March 2023 (4 years 3 months)

Bladel, Noord-Brabant, Australia

- Brought in the user perspective to many successfully launched projects.
- Consult with project managers, business analysis and development teams on application development and business plans.
- Provides strategic and technical assistance to Management on architectural strategies by evaluating approaches and alternatives.
- Tested website and performed troubleshooting prior to deployment.
- Handled whole projects from scratch idea to production deployment.

Elait

FullStack Developer

June 2016 - January 2019 (2 years 8 months)

Mount Waverley, Victoria, Australia

- Leading and managing a team of 4 developers
- · Developing internal ERP software
- Working on integration with REST based company's gateways and third party software
- Working in Agile environment using scrum methodology

VIEWPOINT CONSTRUCTION SOFTWARE LTD Frontend Web Developer

Page 1 of 2

March 2014 - August 2016 (2 years 6 months)

Chatswood, New South Wales, Australia

- Getting Requirements, Analyzing the Requirements
- Using tech stack of Laravel, Codeigniter MVC Framework, Drupal, MySql, Git, jQuery, Ajax, Bootstrap
- Single-handedly building front-end and the back-end of many sites.
- A Codelgniter based CMS for Tripzy.ae and a CMS for B3adventures using the PHP Codelgniter, Bootstrap.

Education

Swinburne University of Technology

Bachelor's degree, Computer and Information Sciences and Support Services · (March 2011 - September 2014)